<resources>

    <!-- App -->
    <string name="app_name">Chrissi Island</string>
    <string name="content_description">image</string>

    <!-- Fragments names -->
    <string name="frag_one">Welcome</string>
    <string name="frag_two">About</string>
    <string name="frag_three">Travel</string>
    <string name="frag_four">Highlights</string>
    <string name="frag_five">Rules</string>

    <!-- Welcome page -->
    <string name="welcome_title">Are you ready for an adventure?</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Do you want to feel for a while like a modern castaway, stranded on a desert island?</string>
    <string name="welcome_button">Yes</string>

    <!-- Welcome fragment -->
    <string name="welcome0">Then welcome to Chrissi Island.</string>
    <string name="welcome1">Chrissi Island, also known as Chryssi or Gaidouronnisi, is a secluded, isolated, almost tropical island on the most southern end of Crete.</string>
    <string name="welcome2">Chrissi is a piece of paradise on Earth. It is the southernmost natural park of Europe, and a gem of the Mediterranean.</string>
    <string name="welcome_section">Chrissi Island.</string>

    <!-- About fragment -->
    <string name="about0">The island of Chrissi is situated approximately 9 nautical miles south of Lerapetra</string>
    <string name="about1">Due to its incredible natural beauty and important ecosystem, it is under the protection of the European initiative NATURA 2000, as a wildlife refuge and an "area of intense natural beauty".</string>
    <string name="about2">The island is only an hour cruise away from the port of Lerapetra.</string>
    <string name="about3">It has an area of 4,743 square kilometers, and a maximum altitude of 27 meters.</string>
    <string name="about4">It\'s an islet known for its exotic waters in all the shades of blue and green.</string>
    <string name="about5">The golden beaches, made of fossilized shell beach is where the island got it name from.</string>
    <string name="about6">The island has a Cedar forrest which extends to the center of Chrissi, covering an area of 350,000 square meters, which is one-fourth of the island.</string>
    <string name="about7">The island Cedar forrest are protected and are over 200-300 years old.</string>
    <string name="about8">The island as a spectacular collection of mainly grey-green, reddish-brown and black rocks.</string>
    <string name="about9">The base rocks of Chrissi were created through the solidification of lava that poured out of an undersea volcano millions of years ago.</string>
    <string name="about10">The 49 species of fossils (corals, shells, barnacles, urchins) found on the island comes from the sea.</string>
    <string name="about11">The northern shores of the island are Belegrina, Hatzivolakas, and Kataprosopo, and are filled with shells.</string>
    <string name="about12">The scenic chapel of Agios Nikolaos and the island\'s lighthouse are located West of Hatzivolakas.</string>
    <string name="about13">On the northeast of the church, there is an old salt marsh and the island\'s only house, bulit atop of ancient remnants.</string>
    <string name="about14">There a wells and carved tombs on the south and southwest of Agios Nikolaos, with the biggest tomb dating back to the Roman era.</string>
    <string name="about15">Kataprosopo faces the Mikronisi islet, on the east of Chrissi, and is a habitat for thousands of birds.</string>




    <!-- Travel fragment -->


    <!-- Highlights fragment -->


    <!-- Rules fragment -->
    <string name="dont1">Hike outside the designated paths and beaches</string>
    <string name="dont2">Collect rocks, fossils, shells and ancient finds</string>
    <string name="dont3">Collect plant or do any animal cathcing</string>
    <string name="dont4">Start a fire or smoke around the bushes and woodlands</string>

    <!-- placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
